kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
Missing the Point
The Target is Coming Into View
Naruto, Choji, gather all of them!
I know!
Yeah!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Over here!
Over there!
Don't lose any of them!
Yeah!
Pick it up!
Over there!
Go over there!
Hey that's mine!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Arm!
Where did that bird go?
Damn it! We lost it!
Over there!
Just a little more...
This is a mission believe it or not!
This is something very important...
I beg you...
Please let go of it!
We have trouble, Tsunade-sama!
What is it?!
Those papers
scattered throughout the village,
are the plans that were stolen
from the carpenter boss.
Currently, Shikamaru and his team
have finished collecting all the plans,
and rechecking them.
But it seems like they have
collected all of them.
What is the meaning of this?
I have no idea...
Tsunade-sama! We have a report
from those who headed to
the Hidden Waterfall Village!
Was there movement?!
Actually, it turns out that it was only
a large-scale practice run!
They are saying that they see
no signs of an invasion of Leaf Village.
What?!
It seems as though they have
already finished their practice run,
and the Hidden Waterfall Village
is back to normal.
So Genno and Hidden Waterfall Village
have nothing to do with each other...?
Disengage the S-Level
Emergency Security Alert!
Order all forces back to village!
Yes!
What in the world
was that man plotting?!
Tsunade-sama!
What now?!
The body that
the ANBU Black Ops gathered...
It's...
It's not Genno...?
What does that mean?
But I thought that Old Man Genno was
cornered by the ANBU Black Ops
and blew himself up.
He traded places with a corpse that
he had ready right before the explosion...
That's a huge possibility!
We're in the middle of confirming that!
Their appearances look similar,
but small details bring up questions!
Most likely, it's another man.
Are you telling me
he fooled the ANBU Black Ops?
That means, Genno is...
He's still alive!
Damn! What is that man up to?
Over there. Behind that tree.
It's here!
I see. The old man Genno used
this hole to get away.
He camouflaged it well.
If it wasn't for the Byakugan,
we would have missed it.
Not only that...
This hole is made so that it closes
naturally by the weight of the earth.
If we came here another day later,
it would have been
extremely difficult to find,
even with the Byakugan.
And to prove that,
you can barely see any sign of
an entrance to this hole.
Akamaru, can you follow his scent?
He's even got getting rid of
his smell covered...
Where could he have gone?
Our conclusion is that...
Old Man Genno is still alive
and there's a possibility that
he's hiding in Leaf Village.
He got cornered,
and faked his own suicide,
and stole the plans so that he could...
make all of us turn our eyes outside
of the village.
He could have already known
about the big practice run
in the Hidden Waterfall Village
and used that to his advantage.
But the ANBU Black Ops
started to mark Genno because
they happened to find out that his letter
of recommendation was a fake, right?
Was it a coincidence...?
Isn't it strange that
a real letter of recommendation was
at the house of the carpenter boss
he worked for?
Then what is his true goal?
If we knew the answer to that,
we wouldn't be struggling so much...
Shikamaru!
The only thing I can say now is...
The number of Shinobi in this village
currently is at its lowest ever.
We only have a bare minimum
of us here!
And most of their eyes are
looking outside of the village.
Even if Genno was walking around
as he was humming on the streets,
no one would suspect anything of him.
Did he set a trap in the village?!
Could the fact that
he scattered the plans around mean
he's already done setting his trap?
No, this is just a diversion
to turn our eyes.
We can't leave this place
without any security,
but we have few people...
Then where do we look?
The Academy.
The Academy?
Why the Academy out of all
the important facilities in the village?
Out of all the sites Genno worked on,
only the Academy's repair plan
was stolen.
It's hard to think that
it was a coincidence
for it to disappear at this timing.
Byakugan!
Well?
There's nothing in this room.
Then... move ahead to the next room.
Byakugan!
Seems like there's nothing in this area.
Can't you look at
the entire campus at once?
And we have Hinata too, you know?
That would be possible
if we know what the target was,
but we're looking for
something suspicious.
We'll have to take the basic route.
Hey! Wait a minute!
You're in the way!
And there's too many... people here.
Like I said!
All I want is for you guys to come outside
even just for a moment!
Our teacher told us to study on our own
in the classroom for today!
We can't go out of the room!
There are no teachers today!
So nobody would know
if you left the class!
We used to skip class when
Iruka-sensei wasn't looking
when we were younger.
Oh, a delinquent!
Delinquent!
We have to check this area!
Besides, all the teachers have gone
on a mission to protect the village.
Why are you guys still here?
They must be useless.
What did you say?!
We're also protecting the village too...
Naruto. You're wasting time
Let's crush them!
What?
The Expansion Jutsu!
We're going to tell on you to our teacher!
Yeah, do as you please!
Idiot!
Let's practice our Kunai Knives.
Sounds good.
It doesn't seem like
there's anything suspicious...
Hurry up!
Wait!
Come on.
I'm begging you to leave!
Naruto!
Where did those kids from
the next classroom go?
I don't know...
They were going to practice
their Kunai Knives.
That's what they were saying.
Oh, yeah, yeah. That's right.
They're practicing their Kunai Knives
in a place like that?
I'll do next.
Ok. Do your best!
Do it!
Yeah!
Oh, so close.
They really are practicing...
When we were
students at the Academy,
we used to skip class and come here.
The teachers couldn't find us here,
it really was great!
I read manga, and took naps...
That's right, I ate potato chips.
Well, that's no good!
You can learn something from those kids.
Even if the teachers don't see you,
you should still commit to your practice!
They're true models of students!
Wonderful!
I'm excited! I'm moved!
I'd like to take class with them!
We wouldn't want to interrupt.
Let's go.
Yeah...
Naruto...
What?
Did they have that before?
I'm going to get this one!
Ouch!
I had it!
It seems pretty new.
Genno could have made it...
I'm going to get Neji or Hinata!
You guys get out of the way.
You're getting in the way of our practice.
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm next!
Byakugan!
It's a Paper Bomb!
It's hidden behind the wall!
What, inside the wall?!
It's completely hidden inside the wall.
But then how do you
detonate it...?
Oh, there she is.
Hey! Hinata!
Naruto.
Naruto...
Hinata, go out with me!
What are you saying
at a time like this?!
I don't know... Go out with you?
You won't?
I'm not necessarily saying no...
Then I'll just ask Neji then.
See you later!
What?
There's a thin thread attached
to the Paper Bomb.
A thread?
It's probably a special thread
used to ignite it.
He's probably is going to detonate it
from a distance...
Where is that thread connected to?!
It goes around the classroom and...
It goes outside...
towards the training hall...?
There's a log standing...
This... Could it be?!
Neji! Come with me for a second!
What is it!
We're in the middle of something...
Actually there's a strange log standing
in the training hall over there.
We wanted him to check it.
That's the triggering device!
Try loosening up your shoulders
and then throw it.
Shut up.
All right, I'm up next.
There should be a target on the log.
Yeah, there is.
The center of the target
is the triggering device!
When a Kunai Knife hits the center...
the device will activate...
And the Academy will explode!
So close!
If you focus, you'll hit the target.
All right, I'm going to hit this time.
Focus...
And target!
Don't let anybody hit the target!
All right, I hit the target!
You did it!
Oh?
The tip is cracked. You always
have to take care of your tools.
Damn, I thought that I hit the target.
This way! Behind there!
All right...
I'm going to hit it for sure!
That's the spirit!
This looks good!
This time I'm going to hit it!
Bushy Brow!
Stop it, Lee!
What?
Oh, did I scare you?
I'm sorry. I just dropped my ninja tool...
Here.
Bushy Brow, you did it!
I had the target!
Why did you get in the way?!
Be quiet!
If that had hit the target,
the Academy would have exploded!
What...?
For real?
A triggering device in here, huh?
When something hits the center,
the Academy explodes.
So there hasn't been anyone
who's been able to hit the center.
We really were lucky.
We were lucky, huh?
So who started to practice
throwing their Kunai Knife here?
Who? Who was it?
Somebody told us that we'd be praised
if we got better at Kunai Knife throwing
in secret from the teachers.
"In secret from from the teachers..."
Whoever must have used Genjutsu
to make them think that.
It must be Genno.
What happened?
Well... There's more than one thread
coming out of the triggering device.
Is that true, Hinata?
Yeah...
Byakugan!
True. There's not just one...
Two... no, three?
Where are they connected to?
Outside of the Academy... No!
Wait! It's hard to see from here.
Me too...
Byakugan!
I found one.
I found one, too
Tell us the location.
No, wait.
The thread splits again.
Over here too...
This is...
No way...
It can't be...
Hey! What's the matter!
There's Paper Bombs planted
all over the village!
It's not just 10 or 20...
It's countless numbers of them!
What?!
The Village Hidden in the Leaves
is a nest of Paper Bombs!
hoshikuzu suchasucha sucha odoru
on a checkerboard night
ichimatsu no yoru ni
when the stardust's are rapidly dancing
aa mada kaeri takunai to kuchi ni wa dasenai naa
I just can't come out and say, "ah, I don't want to go home yet"
omowa seburi terii
suggestively
aisubeki kao ni tsuba wo misutaa kuriketto
spat at that beloved face, mister cricket
asekusai suteeji no ue de hikaru toronboon no
the trombone gradually going off-key
picchi ga dandan hazureteitteiru no mo kininaru kedo
while on the sweaty center stage does bug me
sonna koto yori kono nai mune no moyamoya wa sakki
but more importantly, the fuzziness I feel in my undeveloped chest,
nonda koora no sei kashira nee
I wonder If it's from that coke I just drank?
— Now, the Academy is safe.
— All right!
It's too early to feel relieved.
If he realizes the Paper Bombs
are being deactivated,
he might blow up the village
by a different method.
Then we have to evacuate
everyone quickly!
— Then he'll know what we're doing!
— That means...
Pretend we don't notice anything
and get rid of the Paper Bombs.
Everyone, get to it at once!
— Yeah!
— Yes.
Next time:
"Still Active! The Best Helper."